- Are you ready, kids?
- 孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
all:
Aye, aye, Captain.
全部：
是的，是的，船长。
- I can't hear you.
- 我听不到你说话。
all:
Aye, aye, Captain.
全部：
是的，是的，船长。
- ♪ Ohh... ♪
- ♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants.
全部：
海绵宝宝。
- ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
- ♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants.
全部：
海绵宝宝。
- ♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
- ♪ 如果航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants.
全部：
海绵宝宝。
- ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
- ♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
all: SpongeBob SquarePants.
- Ready?
所有：海绵宝宝。
- 准备好？
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants.
全部：
海绵宝宝。
SpongeBob SquarePants.
- SpongeBob
- 海绵宝宝
SquarePants.
方裤。
[laughing]
[笑]
♪ ♪
[waves crashing]
[海浪拍打]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
- [grumbling]
- [抱怨]
Where's that bus?
那辆公共汽车在哪里？
I've been waiting for
almost an hour.
我一直在等待
差不多一个小时。
- Heh. Almost an hour he says.
- 呵呵。他说差不多一个小时了。
- Hmm.
- 唔。
Late again.
又迟到了。
One coin.
一枚硬币。
Exact change.
- Aha.
确切的改变。
- 啊哈。
- Exactly.
- 确切地。
Late.
晚的。
- Oh, brother.
- 哦，兄弟。
- Will you please watch
your speed?
- 请你看一下好吗
你的速度？
And stay in the lane.
并留在车道上。
When was the last time you
cleaned this bus?
上次你是什么时候
清理了这辆公共汽车吗？
[sniffing]
Ew, it smells like
[嗅嗅]
呃，闻起来像
a narwhal's armpit in here.
这里有独角鲸的腋窝。
- All right, that's it.
- 好吧，就是这样。
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
- Krusty Krab.
- 蟹堡王。
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
[grumbling]
[抱怨]
You big clod.
你这个大土包。
I could do your job better than
you ever could.
我可以比你做得更好
你曾经可以。
- Yeah? Well, I could do your
job better than you ever could.
- 是的？好吧，我可以做你的
工作比你以前能做的更好。
What's his job?
他的工作是什么？
- Oh, he's a terrible cashier.
- 哦，他是个糟糕的收银员。
- That I could do.
- 我能做到的。
- All right, all right.
- 好吧，好吧。
Jumpin' jelly fish.
跳跃的水母。
I'm tired of you two
bickering every morning.
我厌倦了你们两个
每天早上都吵架。
I say prove it.
我说证明一下。
Switch jobs right now and
settle it once and for all.
立即换工作并
一劳永逸地解决它。
- I'll take that challenge.
- 我会接受这个挑战。
- You better get going, driver.
- 你最好走吧，司机。
You're already behind schedule.
你已经落后于计划了。
[both grumbling]
[两人都抱怨]
- Hmm.
- 唔。
Ahh.
啊。
[groaning]
[呻吟]
[gasps]
[喘气]
[tires squealing]
[轮胎吱吱声]
all: Whoa-oh! Whoa-oh!
全体：哇哦！哇哦！
- ♪ La-da-dee la-dah-dah ♪
- ♪ 拉达迪拉达达 ♪
Oh, I like this.
哦，我喜欢这个。
Good morning.
早上好。
- It's afternoon already,
clown.
- 已经是下午了
小丑。
Eh, ah-ah.
呃，啊啊。
No sharp objects allowed.
不允许使用尖锐物体。
- [munching]
- Huh?
- [咀嚼]
- 啊？
Attention: this is your
cheerful driver speaking.
注意：这是你的
开朗的司机说话。
There'll be no eating or
drinking
不会有东西吃或者
饮酒
aboard my happy bus...
登上我快乐的巴士...
- Ohh.
- 哦。
Especially Krabby Patties.
尤其是蟹肉饼。
This stop is Coral Boulevard.
这一站是珊瑚大道。
Thank you for riding with your
merry bus driver.
感谢您与您一起骑行
快乐的巴士司机。
And have
a beautiful da--hey.
并且有
一个美丽的达——嘿。
- Squidward.
- 章鱼哥。
- No!
- 不！
- It's you.
- 是你。
- [grumbling]
- [抱怨]
- I've always dreamed one day
I'd board a bus
- 我一直梦想着有一天
我会搭巴士
and see you driving it.
看看你驾驶它。
- Why am I in that dream?
- 为什么我会在那个梦里？
- Oh, Squidward, you're in all
my dreams.
-哦，章鱼哥，你就是一切
我的梦想。
- Get off me and pay your fare.
- 下车并付车费。
And you'd better have--huh?
你最好——嗯？
- Exact change. Exactly.
- 确切的改变。确切地。
Clink, clink, clink, clink,
叮当，叮当，叮当，叮当，
clink, clink, clink, clink.
叮当，叮当，叮当，叮当。
- Augh! Enough with the
pennies!
- 啊啊！够了
便士！
- Clink, clink, clink, clink,
clink, clink.
- 叮当，叮当，叮当，叮当，
叮当，叮当。
[humming]
[嗡嗡声]
Hey, Squidward.
嘿，章鱼哥。
- [grumbling]
- Hey, Squidward.
- [抱怨]
- 嘿，章鱼哥。
Hey, Squidward.
嘿，章鱼哥。
- What?
- 什么？
- I'm helping you drive.
- 我帮你开车。
- No, you're not.
- 不，你不是。
- Time to switch lanes.
- 是时候换道了。
Better use my signal.
最好用我的信号。
[clicking tongue]
[咂舌]
- Oh, oh, oh, oh-ah, ah!
- 哦，哦，哦，哦，啊，啊！
Ahh!
啊！
Don't help me drive!
别帮我开车！
- Okay.
- 好的。
[tires squealing]
[轮胎吱吱声]
Wow.
- Ahh, eh eh, eh.
哇。
- 啊，呃呃，呃。
Whew.
呼。
Oh, what am I doing?
哦，我在做什么？
Sit in the back.
坐在后面。
- Okay.
- 好的。
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
- What--what the...
- 什么--什么...
[sighs]
Ahh!
[叹气]
啊！
- Objects in mirror are closer
than they appear.
- 镜子中的物体更近
比他们出现的要多。
Aw, let me help.
噢，让我帮忙。
This is for softer braking.
这是为了更柔和的制动。
- Augh,
the brakes don't work.
- 噢，
刹车不起作用。
Ahh-ahh!
啊啊啊！
Augh!
啊啊！
[engine revving]
[发动机转速]
Argh!
啊！
[tires screeching]
[轮胎的尖叫声]
[grunts]
[咕哝]
- Mmph! Huh? Argh.
- 嗯！啊？啊。
Argh!
- Oh!
啊！
- 哦！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[all grunting]
[全都咕哝]
- SpongeBob, what is
your stop,
- 海绵宝宝，什么是
你的停靠站，
so I can take you there right
now?
这样我就可以带你去那里
现在？
- Oh, I don't have a stop.
- 哦，我没有停下来。
Today is my bus riding day,
今天是我搭巴士的日子
the day I just pick a bus and
ride it all day.
那天我刚选了一辆公共汽车
骑它一整天。
- There's only one
thing I can think of
- 只有一个
我能想到的事
that could be worse.
那可能会更糟。
Ahhhh!
啊啊啊！
- [chuckling]
- [轻笑]
- Augh! And that's it!
- 啊啊！就是这样！
- [chuckling]
- [轻笑]
[babbling]
[胡说]
- Phew. I dodged that one.
Heh-heh.
- 唷。我躲开了那个。
呵呵。
Augh!
啊啊！
- [chuckling]
- [轻笑]
Ehh-ehh-ehh.
呃呃呃。
[tires squealing]
[轮胎吱吱声]
[all shouting]
[大家大喊]
[tires squealing]
[轮胎吱吱声]
- Phew. That was close.
- 唷。那很接近了。
- It sure was.
- 确实如此。
I almost didn't catch this bus.
我差点没赶上这趟公共汽车。
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
- Eeeee...Patrick. Wow.
- 呃…帕特里克。哇。
We're both on the
same bus on our
我们都在
我们的同一辆巴士
Just Riding Around
On The Bus Day.
只是骑车到处走走
在巴士日。
What are the odds?
几率有多大？
[both chuckling]
[两人都笑了]
- Yes, what are the odds?
- 是的，可能性有多大？
- I got my bus money
somewhere.
- 我拿到了公交车钱
某处。
- Oh.
- Oh, there it is.
- 哦。
- 哦，就在那里。
Huh, I think I left my
wallet in my other wallet.
呵呵，我想我离开了我的
钱包在我的另一个钱包里。
- Don't worry, buddy.
-别担心，伙计。
I've got exact change.
我有零钱。
- One...
- 一...
Two...
- [groaning]
两个...
- [呻吟]
- Three.
- 三。
- ♪ Dah-dah-dah-dum ♪
- ♪ 哒哒哒哒 ♪
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[tires squealing]
[轮胎吱吱声]
- [chuckling]
- [轻笑]
- You hooligans.
- 你们这些流氓。
- Ugh! Augh!
- 呃！啊啊！
[tires squealing]
[轮胎吱吱声]
[explosions]
[爆炸]
- And now SpongeBob
will attempt to catch
- 现在是海绵宝宝
会尝试抓住
his high-flying partner
Patrick
他的雄心勃勃的伙伴
帕特里克
while swinging from the
strap of death.
当从
死亡带。
- Hey-oh!
- 嘿-哦！
[together]
Whoo. Whoa.
[一起]
呼。哇哦。
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
[both grunting]
[两人都咕哝着]
- Ooh...oof!
- 哦...哦！
- Awwww. Ohh, yes.
- 哇哦。哦，是的。
- Lady, get that horrible
thing off your lap.
- 女士，变得太可怕了
东西离开你的腿。
- I'll do no such thing.
- 我不会做这样的事。
He's my emotional support
animal.
他是我情感上的依靠
动物。
Oh, yes, aren't you?
哦，是的，你不是吗？
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
[barking]
[叫声]
- Ohh.
- 哦。
- [snarling]
- [咆哮]
Rah!
啊！
[both snarling and barking]
[咆哮和吠叫]
- My leg! Oh!
- 我的腿！哦！
[both snarling and barking]
[咆哮和吠叫]
[all groaning]
[全都呻吟]
[tires squealing]
[轮胎吱吱声]
- [grumbling]
- [抱怨]
- [burps]
- [打嗝]
- [grumbling]
- [抱怨]
That's it!
就是这样！
I am throwing you two off right
now.
我要把你们两个扔掉
现在。
[grumbling]
[抱怨]
Where's that pink pinhead?
那个粉红色的针头在哪里？
- Oh, he's in the restroom.
- Huh?
- 哦，他在洗手间里。
- 啊？
That's not a restroom.
那不是卫生间。
It's the emergency exit.
这是紧急出口。
[toilet flushing]
[冲厕所]
Augh!
啊啊！
- You're out of toilet paper.
- 你的卫生纸用完了。
Who's driving?
Well, I am, of course.
谁在开车？
嗯，我当然是。
Wah!
哇！
[tires squealing]
[轮胎吱吱声]
all: Ahh!
全体：啊！
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- This bus isn't designed for
the pressure at these depths.
- 这辆巴士不是为
这些深度的压力。
- Ohh!
- Ahh!
- 哦！
- 啊！
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- Aw, look at you.
- 噢，看看你。
- [chuckling]
- [轻笑]
Look at you.
看看你。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- We're gonna be crushed
to death.
- 我们会被压垮
至死。
I don't wanna drive a bus.
我不想开公共汽车。
- I don't wanna be crushed.
- 我不想被压垮。
- I don't wanna eat
this sandwich.
-我不想吃饭
这个三明治。
Ooh, a panini, so
very continental.
哦，帕尼尼，所以
非常欧陆式。
[munching]
[咀嚼]
- Hey, look, a passenger. Hi.
- 嘿，看，一位乘客。你好。
- [gasps]
- [喘气]
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
[tires squealing]
[轮胎吱吱声]
- I don't know where we're
going.
- 我不知道我们在哪里
去。
- Don't worry. I have a bus
map.
- 不用担心。我有一辆公共汽车
地图。
Take a left. Take another left.
向左转。再左转。
Left. Left. Left.
左边。左边。左边。
Left. Left, left, left.
- I can't see.
左边。左，左，左。
- 我看不到。
- We don't need to see.
- 我们不需要看到。
We just need to believe.
我们只需要相信。
- I believe your map
is upside down.
- 我相信你的地图
是颠倒的。
- Oh, I can fix that.
- 哦，我可以解决这个问题。
[both grunting]
[两人都咕哝着]
Ahh!
啊！
- Back of the line, people.
- 队伍后面的人。
Back of the line.
排在后面。
[all shouting]
[大家大喊]
- Ohh.
Exact change only, please.
- 哦。
请仅进行精确更改。
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
Huh?
啊？
all: Ugh!
全体：呃！
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
That settles it.
这样就解决了。
I quit everything.
我放弃了一切。
- Huh?
- 啊？
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
- The Krusty Krab Local right
on time.
- Krusty Krab 当地权利
准时。
One Krabby Patty, please.
请来一份蟹肉饼。
- One Krabby Patty?
- 一份蟹肉饼？
Yes, sir. One Krabby Patty.
是的，先生。一份蟹肉饼。
- One Krabby Patty coming up.
- 一只蟹肉饼即将上来。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- Place your orders, everybody.
- 大家下订单吧。
Because no one can do this job
better than me.
因为没有人能胜任这项工作
比我好。
I win.
我赢了。
[toilet flushing]
[冲厕所]
all: Huh?
全体：啊？
- You're still out of
toilet paper.
- 你还没出局
卫生纸。